bringvisitor.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy

**How BV(Bringvisitor.com) Uses Your Personal Information**  
---  
This policy covers how BV treats personal information that BV collects and receives, including information related to your past use of BV products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.  
**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**  
BV collects personal information when you register with BV, when you use BV products or services, when you visit BV pages or the pages of certain BV partners. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address. When you register with BV and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. BV automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request. BV uses information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, and contact you.   
**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**  
BV does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested.   
**COOKIES**  
BV may set and access cookies on your computer. BV uses web beacons to access BV cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with BV products and services.   
**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**  
You can edit your BV Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. New categories of marketing communications might be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the BV service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the BV Newsletter, that are considered part of your BV account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. You can delete your BV account by visiting our Account Deletion page.   
**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**  
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
